It's been two weeks since the CJP
protest ended. [laughter]
>> I think it's safe to say it's been
rather successful.
>> Yeah. Like after a lot of back and
forth, eventually the government had to
hold the protesters accountable.
[laughter]
>> [applause]
[clears throat]
>> And in doing so, we were reminded of a
longforgotten virtue of democracy, which
is you cannot abuse the prime minister's
mother. [laughter]
Are we clear? [laughter]
You cannot abuse the prime minister's
mother like his followers abuse yours.
[laughter]
>> [applause]
>> THE empire struck back.
[laughter]
>> We did not like the taste of humble pie.
There was too much beef.
[laughter]
So they did what anybody in their
position would do. They had to, you
know, make an example of somebody,
right? So they decided to target a
15year-old girl.
Yeah. They called this campaign beta.
[laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> Now any normal human being with a
beating heart would ask like know why
would you use state apparatus to go
after a 15year-old?
But you must understand that this is not
just any political party.
These guys are the best of the best.
[laughter]
They are pioneers. [laughter]
For them, age is just a number.
It doesn't [laughter] matter if you're
15 years old or if you died 62 years
ago.
[applause]
If it suits them, they will target you.
They do not discriminate
and that is what a democracy is all
about.
So what did this 15year-old do? There
was a video of her on social media where
she was abusing the prime minister. Did
you watch that video?
>> Yeah. Even I watched it. I was like
[laughter]
damn girl.
And keep in mind that a lot of the abuse
towards the prime minister started after
the protesters were ly charged.
>> Now I don't know if you live in the same
world as me [laughter]
but if you hit somebody with a stick
they are not going to have nice stuff to
say about you. [laughter]
And mind you this particular video was
not the only one. There were hundreds of
videos coming out from across the
country while they were all abusing the
prime minister. And a lot of these
people who were abusing the prime
minister also had penises. [laughter]
But
for some strange reason, they decided to
target this particular girl. I guess she
reminded them that some things in life
will always be unattainable. [laughter]
Right.
>> So they they went after her, they
harassed her, they posted her details
online, they threatened her with rape,
they threatened her with murder. The
cops filed an FIR. [laughter]
And eventually this girl broke and she
posted an apology video online which is
where she revealed she was 15 years old.
I mean, think about this, right? They
targeted a 15year-old girl to plade the
ego of a 56 in chest. [laughter]
[laughter]
Now once everybody found out she was
just 15, somebody had to do damage
control. So, the country's best FRIEND
[laughter]
dropped another REEL [laughter]
where he said that despite his feelings
being hurt, [laughter]
the youth of these protesters are
misguided, which is why he has decided
TO FORGIVE THEM.
>> [laughter]
>> FOR ABUSING his mother and him. He also
wanted to cry on camera, but they were
all out on tear gas. [laughter]
[cheering]
[applause]
And when you think of damage control,
this is what genius moved. It was
absolute genius. Okay, this man got the
protesters beat up, then tried to
gaslight them into thinking that they
were misguided
[laughter] and then he became the victim
and now he has forgiven them. [laughter]
Is it just me or does Modi sound like an
ex we all used to know [laughter]
at some point? [laughter]
>> [clears throat]
>> But after the apology was posted, the
harassment didn't stop. Yeah. Because
the these trolls, you know, I think
trolls was al also showing them too much
respect.
[laughter]
How about we call them dung beatetles
with Wi-Fi? [laughter]
>> Does that work?
>> Yeah.
So these dung beatetles with Wi-Fi,
right, they saw the apology video and
they were like, "No,
that is not the same girl." [laughter]
And then all of them used their
expertise in forensic science [laughter]
and dude they they they
did a structural analysis
of her face. Did you see those images
they posted? They had screen grabs of
both uh videos online and then they
started drawing x-axis and yaxis and
some circles just to prove that her
right ear was not identical to her left
ear. [laughter]
It's genius.
Yeah. And if you look at the the these
images right and if you zoom in just
keep zooming in you will see an image of
bridge bushan singing just smiling
[laughter]
they didn't stop harassing her dude they
they kept abusing her they kept
threatening her and this poor girl just
wanted to be left alone in silence she
didn't want anybody to talk about her so
she had to flee to Manipur
>> [applause and cheering]
>> Okay.
But the empire wasn't done. They decided
to go after everybody. [laughter]
They went after Meta.
They were angry with Meta because a
Facebook video of the prime minister was
deleted for a few hours, right? And then
Meta responded by saying it was just an
accident. You know like the kind of
accidents that happen when files
mysteriously catch fire
but they were not pleased. So there was
a parliamentary committee that demanded
that Mark Zuckerberg apologize
otherwise the prime minister would
forgive him. [laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> This was a wellcoordinated attack if you
were paying attention right. Everybody
played their part. Even the media played
[clears throat] their part. They they
were asking very important questions.
Yeah. Questions like how did Abhiji Dipk
get funding for his foreign education?
[laughter]
His parents are not ministers.
How is Sorovas paying his rent?
Why are they wearing jockey and not VIP?
[laughter]
And there was also these uh
investigative reporters on ground who
were like, you know, creeping around
Sorov Das's house. Did you see that?
>> Right. They're trying to peek through
the windows to see if they could find a
forensic audit of PM cares. You know
this
[laughter]
and professional tapeworm Arnab Gowami.
He's smoking some excellent
[laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> Hurry up.
There's another show after this.
[laughter]
Dude, Arnab is obsessed with this theory
that there is a deep state network,
[laughter]
right? This invisible cabal of players
somewhere that that is hellbent on, you
know, creating anarchy in India. And I'm
just like somebody needs to tell him
that the problem is not deep state
network. It is surface state network.
[laughter]
And of course these Bollywood
celebrities cannot miss a news cycle.
They have to say something, right? They
were feeling left out,
right? I cannot understand what is up
with all this ass kissing.
There was this um yesterday year's TV
actor Sudesh Berry [laughter]
who in an interview said that he wants
to wash the prime minister's feet and
then drink that water. [laughter]
He has not understood swajbara daban.
[laughter]
And I was discussing this with my friend
and she without missing a beat said why
stop at his feet. [laughter]
I was too scared to ask which DIRECTION
SHE MEANT. [laughter]
AND THEN UH shake a R Madwan.
[laughter]
>> Yeah. Allegedly said that it is his duty
to support the prime minister.
This is a man whose duty is also to read
from a script. [laughter]
Look, we got to just make something very
clear, okay? It is not your duty to
support the prime minister. It is your
duty to hold him accountable.
Right? So that situations do not go out
of hand where you eventually have to
take your family and move to Dubai or
something. [laughter]
[applause]
You know what I mean?
And then Bumi Pediger woke up one
morning [laughter]
and decided that she wanted to be
relevant again. [laughter]
So she posted a video where she's like,
"Hey guys, it is okay to protest and all
that, you know, but what is this
language? [laughter]
This bad abusive language is not part of
our culture. Not part of our culture.
What are you French? [laughter]
Remembering mothers and sisters is a
national pastime. [laughter]
[applause]
And have you noticed this is what
society does right? Every time they
don't like something that you say or do,
they will try to shame you by saying
that this is not part of our culture.
And culture is spelled C O N T R O L.
[laughter]
any good movement right always inspires
other movements right so what happened
with the CJP protest also it has
inspired protests in other parts of the
country as well so if you've been
noticing right students are now
protesting in schools and and colleges
and and right now there's a very
important protest in Jarken that you
need to pay attention to right another
movement that was inspired by the CJP
was this movement called reservation
>> [laughter]
>> Alhamdulillah.
These guys protested against reservation
at Jandar Mantur, a site reserved
for protests.
[laughter]
Oh, irony. You beautiful lass.
I think one of the reasons why there's
so much of political chaos in this
country is because a lot of people are
confused about roles.
We
as citizens behave as subjects,
right? We do not treat elected officials
as public servants. We treat them as
rulers.
And I think that is where the biggest
confusion is. The foundational basis of
any democracy is that the people put you
in power. And for all intents and
purposes, technically we are they are
bosses. Is that fair to assume?
>> Yes or no?
>> Right now picture this. Okay, you're at
work. [laughter]
your boss comes to you and says, "Hey,
you know, these very confidential files
have been leaked to the media and we
need to find out how this happened and
we need to hold somebody accountable."
And if your response to that is to beat
your boss UP [laughter]
and then forgive him [laughter]
for asking you that question,
YOU WILL LOSE YOUR JOB. AM I RIGHT?
>> In fact, it will get so bad no other
organization would likely employ you.
Again,
the only job you would then be qualified
for would be prime minister.
[applause]
>> [applause]